Guide to the Alan Farley Collection ARS.0067
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 2001 Book Talk Episodes, 2000-2001; 25 audio cassette tapes (Audio 5)
  B0134; George, Elizabeth; A Traitor to Memory; 7/13/2001; 9/2/2001 (:30)
  B0135; Evans, Nicholas; The Smoke Jumper; 8/27/2001; 9/9/2001 (:30)
  B0136; Winchester, Simon; The Map that Changed the World; 9/10/2001; 9/16/2001 (:30)
  B0137; Roberts, Don; Diaries Of Adam and Eve; 9/6/2001; 9/23/2001 (:30)
  B0138; Linde, Paul; An American Psychiatrist in Africa; 9/20/2001; 9/30/2001 (:30)
  B0139; Franzen, Jonathan; The Corrections; 10/2/2001; 10/28/2001 (:30)
  B0140; Keillor, Garrison; Lake Wobegon Summer 1956; 9/25/2001; 10/14/2001 (:30)
  B0141; Milford, Nancy; Savage Beauty - The Life of Edna St Vincent Millay; 10/1/2001; 10/21/2001 (:23)
  B0142; Gold, Glen David; Carter Beats the Devil; 10/9/2001; 11/4/2001 (:30)
  B0143; Johnson, Haynes; The Best of Times - America in the Clinton Years; 10/24/2001; 11/11/2001 (:30)
  B0144; Gurganus, Allan; The Practical Heart; 10/24/2001; 11/18/2001 (:30)
  B0145; Feiffer, Jules; I'm Not Bobby!; 10/26/2001; 11/25/2001 (:30)
  B0146; Ackerman, Diane; Cultivating Delight; 10/25/2001; 12/2/2001 (:30)
  B0147; Bantock, Nick; Gryphon; 11/14/2001; 12/9/2001 (:20)
  B0148; Allende, Isabel; Portrait in Sepia; 10/29/2001; 12/16/2001 (:30)
  B0149; Thomas, Patricia; Big Shot; 12/3/2001; 12/23/2001 (:30)
  B0150; Morris, Edmund; Theodore Rex; 12/14/2001; 12/30/2001 (:30)
- 2002 Book Talk Episodes, 2001-2002; 22 audio cassette tapes (Audio 6)
  B0201; Gioia, Dana; Poetry Speaks; 12/19/2001; 1/6/2002 (:30)
  B0202; Walters, Suzanna; All the Rage - The Story of Gay Visibility in America; 1/7/2002; 1/13/2002 (:30)
  B0203; Hester, Elliott; Plane Insanity; 1/17/2002; 1/20/2002 (:24)
  B0204; McWhorter, John; The Power of Babel; 1/23/2002; 2/3/2002 (:30)
  B0205; Schlosser, Eric; Fast Food Nation; 1/25/2002; 2/10/2002 (:30)
  B0206; Wu, Frank; Yellow - Race in America Beyond Black and White; 1/30/2002; 2/17/2002 (:30)
  B0207; Trillin, Calvin; Tepper Isn't Going Out; 2/4/2002; 2/24/2002 (:30)
  B0208; Sterry, David Henry; Chicken - Confessions of a Boy for Rent; 2/25/2002; 3/3/2002 (:30)
  B0209; Hayes, Bill; Sleep Demons - An Insomniac's Memoir; 3/4/2002; 3/10/2002 (:30)
  B0210; Basu, Jay; The Stars Can Wait; 3/1/2002; 3/17/2002 (:30)
  B0211; Davis, Wade; Light at the Edge of the World; 3/19/2002; 3/24/2002 (:30)
  B0212; Moore, Christopher; Lamb - The Gospel According to Biff, Christ's Boyhood Pal; 3/28/2002; 3/31/2002 (:30)
  B0213; Gitlin, Todd; Media Unlimited; 3/18/2002; 4/7/2002 (:30)
  B0214; Mosby, Katherine; The Season of Lillian Dawes; 5/1/2002; 5/5/2002 (:30)
  B0215; Smith, Dennis; Report from Ground Zero; 5/4/2002; 5/12/2002 (:30)
  B0216; Rakoff, David; Fraud; 4/29/2002; 5/19/2002 (:30)
  B0217; Donoghue, Emma; The Woman Who Gave Birth to Rabbits; 4/29/2002; 5/26/2002 (:30)
  B0218; Franken, Al; Oh, the Things I Know!; 5/6/2002; 6/2/2002 (:30)
  B0219; Kennedy, Caroline; Profiles in Courage for Our Time; 5/22/2002; 6/9/2002 (:30)
  B0220; Shabazz, Ilyasha; Growing Up X; 5/17/2002; 6/16/2002 (:25)
  B0221; Stone, Elizabeth; A Boy I Once Knew; 5/28/2002; 6/23/2002 (:30)
  B0222; Frayn, Michael; Spies; 4/16/2002; 6/30/2002 (:30)
  B0223; Durham, David Anthony; Walk through Darkness; 5/2/2002; 7/7/2002 (:30)
  B0224; Caro, Robert; Master of the Senate; 5/23/2002; 7/14/2002 (:30)
  B0225; Ross, Lillian; Reporting Back - Notes on Journalism; 6/3/2002; 7/21/2002 (:30)
  B0226; Bernays, Anne; Back Then - New York in the 50s; Kaplan; Justin; 6/20/2002; 7/28/2002 (:30)
  B0227; Carter, Stephen; The Emperor of Ocean Park; 6/13/2002; 8/4/2002 (:30)
  B0228; Hillerman, Tony; The Wailing Wind; 5/29/2002; 8/11/2002 (:30)
  B0229; Levine, Larry; The People and The President; Levine; C; 7/10/2002; 8/18/2002 (:30)
  B0230; Cooper, Dennis; My Loose Thread; 6/13/2002; 8/25/2002 (:25)
  B0231; Emerson, Earl; Updraft; 6/6/2002; 9/1/2002 (:30)
  B0232; Mosley, Walter; Bad Boy Brawly Brown; 7/17/2002; 9/8/2002 (:30)
  B0233; Fatsis, Stefan; Word Freak; 9/5/2002; 9/15/2002 (:30)
  B0234; Strauss, Darin; The Real McCoy; 8/29/2002; 9/22/2002 (:30)
  B0235; Ellis, Kate; Crossing Borders; 9/13/2002; 9/29/2002 (:30)
  B0236; Merwin, William S.; The Mays of Ventadorn; 9/26/2002; 10/13/2002 (:30)
  B0237; Bryant, Howard; Shut Out; 9/19/2002; 10/20/2002 (:30)
  B0238; Barry, Dave; Tricky Business; 10/7/2002; 10/27/2002 (:30)
  B0239; Barker, Clive; Abarat; 10/15/2002; 11/17/2002 (:30)
  B0240; Ondaatje, Michael; The Conversations; 10/7/2002; 11/24/2002 (:30)
  B0241; Goldmark, Kathi; My Shoes Keep Walking Back to You; 10/18/2002; 12/1/2002 (:30)
  B0242; Kurzweil, Allen; The Grand Complication; 9/30/2002; 12/8/2002 (:30)
  B0243; Edmunds, David; Wittgenstein's Poker; 9/30/2002; 12/22/2002 (:30)
  B0244; Nash, Graham; Off the Record; 12/12/2002; 12/29/2002 (:30)
- 2003 Book Talk Episodes, 23 audio cassette tapes (Audio 7)
  B0301; Partridge, Rondal & Elizabeth; Quizzical Eye; 1/2/2003; 1/5/2003 (:30)
  B0302; Bronson, Po; What Should I Do with My Life?; 1/8/2003; 1/12/2003 (:30)
  B0303; Thomson, David; The New Biographical Dictionary of Film; 1/8/2003; 1/19/2003 (:30)
  B0304; Norton, Eleanor Holmes; Fire in the Blood; Lester; Joan Steinau; 1/10/2003; 1/26/2003 (:30)
  B0305; Hertsgaard, Mark; In the Eagle's Shadow; 1/22/2003; 2/2/2003 (:30)
  B0306; Price, Richard; Samaritan; 1/24/2003; 2/9/2003 (:30)
  B0307; Hansen, Ron; Isn't It Romantic?; 1/24/2003; 2/16/2003 (:30)
  B0308; McCann, Colum; Dancer; 2/4/2003; 2/23/2003 (:30)
  B0309; Mosley, Walter; What Next- A Memoir toward World Peace; 2/21/2003; 3/2/2003 (:30)
  B0310; Roszak, Ted; The Devil and Daniel Silverman; 3/3/2003; 3/9/2003 (:30)
  B0311; Boyle, T. C.; Drop City; 3/10/2003; 3/16/2003 (:30)
  B0312; Saperstein, Guy; Civil Warrior - Memoirs of a Civil Rights Attorney; 3/12/2003; 3/30/2003 (:30)
  B0313; Alexander, Robert; The Kitchen Boy - A Novel of the Last Tsar; 3/20/2003; 4/6/2003 (:30)
  B0314; Kennedy, Randall; Interracial Intimacies; 3/24/2003; 4/13/2003 (:30)
  B0315; Fforde, Jasper; Lost in a Good Book; 4/28/2003; 5/4/2003 (:30)
  B0316; Bean, Billy; Going the Other Way; 5/2/2003; 5/11/2003 (:30)
  B0317; Winchester, Simon; Krakatoa - The Day the World Exploded; 5/5/2003; 5/18/2003 (:30)
  B0318; Watson, James; DNA - The Secret of Life; 5/7/2003; 5/25/2003 (:30)
  B0319; Nunberg, Geoffrey; The Way We Talk Now; 4/24/2003; 6/1/2003 (:30)
  B0320; Walton, Todd; Buddha in a Teacup; 5/21/2003; 6/8/2003 (:30)
  B0321; Davis, Jim; Garfield At 25; 6/2/2003; 6/15/2003 (:24)
  B0322; Burroughs, Augusten; Dry; 6/4/2003; 6/22/2003 (:30)
  B0323; Chamberlain, Richard; Shattered Love; 6/10/2003; 6/29/2003 (:30)
  B0324; Dallek, Robert; An Unfinished Life: JFK; 6/4/2003; 7/6/2003 (:30)
  B0325; Halberstam, David; Teammates - Portrait of a Friendship; 6/6/2003; 7/20/2003 (:35)
  B0326; Wong, B. D.; Following Foo; 6/26/2003; 7/20/2003 (:45)
  B0327; MacNeil, Robert; My Country; 6/26/2003; 7/27/2003 (:30)
  B0328; Reed, Ishmael; Three Books; Reed; Timothy; 7/9/2003; 8/3/2003 (:30)
  B0329; Nachman, Gerald; Seriously Funny; 7/15/2003; 8/10/2003 (:30)
  B0330; Berg, A. Scott; Remembering Kate; 7/18/2003; 8/17/2003 (:37)
  B0331; Gleick, James; Isaac Newton; 7/22/2003; 8/24/2003 (:30)
  B0332; Curtis, James; W. C. Fields - A Biography; 7/31/2003; 8/31/2003 (:30)
  B0333; Roberts, Don; The Art of the Bookplate; 8/29/2003; 9/7/2003 (:30)
  B0334; Kiehn, David; Broncho Billy and the Essanay Film Company; 9/10/2003; 9/28/2003 (:30)
  B0335; Eugenidies, Jeffrey; Middlesex; 9/17/2003; 10/5/2003 (:30)
  B0336; Raban, Jonathan; Waxwing; 10/15/2003; 10/19/2003 (:30)
  B0337; Bok, Francis; Escape from Slavery; 10/14/2003; 10/26/2003 (:30)
  B0338; Jones, Edward P.; The Known World; 10/21/2003; 11/2/2003 (:30)
  B0339; Morris, Jan; The World - Travels 1950-2000; 10/30/2003; 11/9/2003 (:30)
  B0340; Tharp, Twyla; Creativity; 10/23/2003; 11/16/2003 (:30)
  B0342; Ivins, Molly; Bushwacked - Life in George W. Bush's America; 10/17/2003; 11/30/2003 (:32)
  B0343; Waters, John; Art - A Sex Book; Hainley; Bruce; 11/21/2003; 12/7/2003 (:30)
  B0344; Albom, Mitch; The Five People You Meet in Heaven; 11/12/2003; 12/14/2003 (:24)
  B0345; Whitehead, Colson; The Colossus Of New York; 11/3/2003; 1/25/2004 (:24)
  B0346; Carey, Peter; My Life as a Fake; 11/17/2003; 12/28/2003 (:30)
- 2004 Book Talk Episodes, 2003-2004; 23 audio cassette tapes (Audio 8)
  B0401; Pierre, DBC; Vernon God Little; 10/24/2003; 1/4/2004 (:30)
  B0402; Macdonald, Ann-Marie; The Way the Crow Flies; 11/20/2003; 1/11/2004 (:30)
  B0403; Blank, Carla; Rediscovering America; 12/17/2003; 1/18/2004 (:30)
  B0404; Auletta, Ken; Backstory; 2/2/2004; 2/8/2004 (:30)
  B0405; Shreeve, James; The Genome War; 2/9/2004; 2/15/2004 (:30)
  B0406; Holland, Merlin; The Real Trial of Oscar Wilde; 2/18/2004; 2/22/2004 (:30)
  B0407; Levenson, Jacob; The Secret Epidemic; 2/19/2004; 2/29/2004 (:41)
  B0408; Fforde, Jasper; The Well of Lost Plots; 2/26/2004; 3/7/2004 (:30)
  B0409; Dunning, John; Bookmans' Promise; 3/4/2004; 3/14/2004 (:30)
  B0410; Greer, Andrew Sean; The Confessions of Max Tivoli; 3/16/2004; 3/21/2004 (:30)
  B0411; Lewis, Michael; Moneyball; 4/1/2004; 4/4/2004 (:30)
  B0412; Ball, Edward; Peninsula of Lies; 3/23/2004; 4/11/2004 (:30)
  B0413; Tucker, Neely; Love in the Driest Season; 3/17/2004; 4/18/2004 (:30)
  B0414; George, Elizabeth; 3/23/2004; 4/25/2004 (:30)
  B0415; Yalom, Marilyn; Birth of the Chess Queen; 4/23/2004; 5/2/2004 (:30)
  B0416; Clark, Mary Higgins; Two Novels; Clark; Carol Higgins; 4/23/2004; 5/9/2004 (:30)
  B0417; Truss, Lynne; Eats, Shoots & Leaves; 4/23/2004; 5/16/2004 (:30)
  B0418; Perin, Margo; How I Learned to Cook; 5/4/2004; 5/23/2004 (:30)
  B0419; Trollope, Joanna; Brother and Sister; 5/10/2004; 5/30/2004 (:30)
  B0420; Lankford, Terrill Lee; Earthquake Weather; 5/12/2004; 6/6/2004 (:30)
  B0421; Roach, Mary; Stiff; 5/18/2004; 6/13/2004 (:30)
  B0422; Lehrer, Jim; New Novels; Lehrer; Kate; 5/27/2004; 6/20/2004 (:30)
  B0423; Osgood, Charles; Defending Baltimore from Enemy Attack; 5/21/2004; 6/27/2004 (:30)
  B0424; Sedaris, David; Dress Your Family in Corduroy and Denim; 6/18/2004; 7/11/2004 (:30)
  B0425; Garland, Alex; The Coma; 6/25/2004; 7/18/2004 (:30)
  B0426; Bly, Robert; The Winged Energy of Desire; 6/23/2004; 7/25/2004 (:30)
  B0427; Mosley, Walter; 7/9/2004; 8/1/2004 (:)
  B0428; Wallace, Marcia; 7/30/2004; 8/8/2004 (:30)
  B0429; Wolfson, Evan; Why Marriage Matters; 8/3/2004; 8/15/2004 (:30)
  B0430; Stahl, Jerry; I, Fatty; 7/28/2004; 8/22/2004 (:30)
  B0431; Steinhauer, Lauren; Sherlock Holmes and the Giant Rats of Sumatra; 8/11/2004; 8/29/2004 (:30)
  B0432; Nunberg, Geoffrey; Going Nucular; 8/11/2004; 9/5/2004 (:30)
  B0433; Collins, Michael; 8/19/2004; 9/26/2004 (:30)
  B0434; Kennedy, Matthew; 9/27/2004; 10/3/2004 (:30)
  B0435; Nyswaner, Ron; 10/5/2004; 10/10/2004 (:30)
  B0436; Saum, Steven; 10/6/2004; 10/17/2004 (:30)
  B0437; Ong, Han; The Dis-Inherited; 10/14/2004; 10/24/2004 (:30)
  B0438; Means, David; The Secret Goldfish; 10/8/2004; 11/7/2004 (:30)
  B0439; Greenblatt, Stephen; Will in the World - How Shakespeare became Shakespeare.;10/20/2004; 11/14/2004 (:30)
  B0440; Tommasini, Anthony; NY Times 100 Best Operas; 10/29/2004; 11/21/2004 (:30)
  B0441; Bogdanovich, Peter; Who the Hell's in It? 10/27/2004; 11/28/2004 (:30)
  B0442; Eymann, Marcia; What's Going On - California and the Vietnam War; 11/10/2004; 12/5/2004 (:30)
  B0443; Klinger, Leslie; The New Annotated Sherlock Holmes; 11/9/2004; 12/12/2004 (:30)
  B0444; Evans, Harold; They Made America; 11/17/2004; 12/19/2004 (:30)
  B0445; Doyle, Roddy; Oh, Play that Thing!; 11/18/2004; 12/26/2004 (:30)
- 2005 Book Talk Episodes, 2004-2005; 25 audio cassette tapes (Audio 9)
  B0501; Mnookin, Seth; Hard Times - The Scandals at the New York Times; 11/19/2004; 1/2/2005 (:30)
  B0502; Thomsom, David; The Whole Equation - A History of Hollywood; 1/7/2005; 1/9/2005 (:30)
  B0503; Thomsom, David; The Whole Equation - A History of Hollywood; 1/7/2005; 1/16/2005 (:30)
  B0504; Leeson, Daniel; The Mozart Forgeries; 12/6/2004; 1/12/2004 (:30)
  B0505; Lescroart, John; The Motive; 1/13/2005; 1/30/2005 (:30)
  B0506; McLarty, Ron; The Memory of Running; 1/21/2005; 2/6/2005 (:30)
  B0507; Hayes, Bill; Five Quarts: A Personal and Natural History of Blood; 2/10/2005; 2/13/2005 (:30)
  B0508; Jackson, Buzzy; A Bad Woman Feeling Good; 2/15/2005; 2/20/2005 (:30)
  B0509; Rarick, Ethan; California Rising; 2/16/2005; 2/27/2005 (:30)
  B0510; Malan, Roy; Efrem Zimbalist: A Life; 2/18/2005; 3/6/2005 (:30)
  B0511; Tippins, Sherill; February House; 2/18/2005; 3/13/2005 (:30)
  B0512; Fasman, Jon; The Geographer's Library; 2/24/2005; 3/20/2005 (:30)
  B0513; Robinson, Peter; Strange Affair; 3/2/2005; 3/27/2005 (:30)
  B0514; Holmes, Rupert; Swing; 3/24/2005; 4/3/2005 (:30)
  B0515; Devlin, Keith; The Math Instinct; 3/28/2005; 4/10/2005 (:30)
  B0516; Goldstein, Rebecca; Incompleteness: The Proof and Paradox of Kurt Godel; 3/22/2005; 5/1/2005 (:30)
  B0517; Ishiguro, Kazuo; Never Let Me Go; 4/25/2005; 5/8/2005 (:30)
  B0518; Apple, R. W. Johnny; Apple's America; 4/29/2005; 5/15/2005 (:3)
  B0519; Lewis, Michael; Coach; 5/12/2005; 5/22/2005 (:30)
  B0520; Maran, Meredith; 50 Ways to Support Gay and Lesbian Equality; 5/23/2005; 5/29/2005 (:25)
  B0521; Rich, Nathaniel; San Francisco Noir; 5/25/2005; 6/5/2005 (:30)
  B0522; Hall, Donald; The Best Day, the Worst Day - Life with Jane Kenyon; 5/17/2005; 6/12/2005 (:30)
  B0523; Kathryn, Shevelow; Charlotte; 5/23/2005; 6/19/2005 (:30)
  B0524; Beasley, Bruce; The Sculpture of Brece Beasley 1960-2005; 6/17/2005; 6/26/2005 (:30)
  B0525; McCullough, David; 1776; 6/20/2005; 7/3/2005 (:30)
  B0526; Evers-Williams, Myrlie; The Autobiography of Medgar Evers; 6/3/2005; 7/10/2005 (:30)
  B0527; Wilsey, Sean; Oh the Glory of It All; 5/31/2005; 7/17/2005 (:30)
  B0528; Leondar-Wright, Betsy; Class Matters; 6/16/2005; 7/24/2005 (:30)
  B0529; Howard, Rachel; The Lost Night; 7/6/2005; 7/31/2005 (:30)
  B0530; Solnit, Rebecca; A Field Guide to Getting Lost; 7/25/2005; 8/7/2005 (:30)
  B0531; Fforde, Jasper; The Big Over Easy; 7/28/2005; 8/14/2005 (:30)
  B0532; Smokler, Kevin; Bookmark Now; 8/2/2005; 8/21/2005 (:30)
  B0533; Jance, J. A.; Long Time Gone; 8/2/2005; 8/28/2005 (:30)
  B0534; Searles, John; Strange but True; 8/23/2005; 9/4/2005 (:30)
  B0535; Ellis, Brett Easton; Lunar Park; 9/9/2005; 9/11/2005 (:30)
  B0536; Rakoff, David;; 9/28/2005; 10/2/2005 (:30)
  B0537; Tilmany, Jack; San Francisco Theatres; 9/12/2005; 10/9/2005 (:30)
  B0538; Roberts, Chris; Heavy Words, Lightly Thrown; 9/8/2005; 10/16/2005 (:30)
  B0539; Winspear, Jacquelline; Pardonable Lies; 9/14/2005; 9/25/2005 (:30)
  B0540; Powers, Ron; Mark Twain - A Life; 10/5/2005; 10/30/2005 (:45)
  B0541; Hollinghurst, Alan; The Line of Beauty; 10/18/2005; 11/6/2005 (:30)
  B0542; Berendt, John; The City of Falling Angels; 10/20/2005; 11/13/2005 (:30)
  B0543; Clarke, Richard; The Scorpion's Gate; 11/2/2005; 11/20/2005 (:30)
  B0544; Moody, Rick; The Diviners; 10/6/2005; 11/27/2005 (:30)
  B0545; Hunter, Tab; Tab Hunter Confidential; 11/1/2005; 12/4/2005 (:30)
  B0546; Wallace, Mike; Between You and Me; 11/4/2005; 12/11/2005 (:30)
  B0547; Truss, Lynne; Talk to the Hand; 11/14/2005; 12/18/2005 (:30)
  B0548; Moehringer, J. R.; The Tender Bar; 11/3/2005; 12/25/2005 (:30)
  B0549; Kimmelman, Michael; Acidental Masterpieces; 9/13/2005; 9/18/2005 (:30)
- 2006 Book Talk Episodes, 2005-2006; 11 audio cassette tapes & 8 digital audio tapes (Audio 10)
  B0601; Morgan, Richard K.; Woken Furies; 11/1/2005; 1/1/2006
  B0602; Gibson, Graeme; The Bedside Book of Birds; 11/4/2005; 1/8/2006
  B0603; Partridge, Elizabeth; John Lennon - An Unauthorized Biography; 12/6/2005; 1/15/2006
  B0604; Lam, Andrew; Perfume Dreams; 1/18/2006; 1/22/2006
  B0605; Lescroart, John; The Hunt Club; 1/27/2006; 1/29/2006
  B0606; Barry, Max; Company; 1/26/2006; 2/5/2006
  B0607; Laird, Nick; Utterly Monkey; 1/30/2006; 2/12/2006
  B0608; Barnes, Julian; Arthur and George; 2/10/2006; 2/19/2006
  B0609; Hodgman, John; The Areas of My Expertise; 2/10/2006; 2/26/2006
  B0610; Fairstein, Linda; Death Dance; 2/2/2006; 3/5/2006
  B0611; Parker, Robert; Death in Paradise; 2/13/2006; 3/12/2006
  B0612; Rapp, Anthony; Without You - A Memoir of Love, Loss and the Musical "Rent"; 2/17/2006; 3/19/2006
  B0613; Yoshino, Kenji; Covering; 2/21/2006; 3/26/2006
  B0614; Crais, Robert; The Two Minute Rule; 2/28/2006; 4/2/2006
  B0615; Stevens, Jr., George; Conversations with the Great Moviemakers of Hollywood's Golden Age; 3/23/2006; 4/9/2006
  B0616; Kushner, Tony; Arthur Miller Play Collection; 3/17/2006; 4/16/2006
  B0617; Franklin, John Hope; Mirror to America; 2/15/2006; 4/23/2006
  B0618; Franklin, John Hope; Mirror to America; 2/15/2006; 4/30/2006
  B0619; Whitehead, Colson; Apex Hides the Hurt; 4/20/2006; 5/7/2006
  B0620; Mann, Robert; Forensic Detective; 4/26/2006; 5/14/2006
  B0621; Johnson, Marilyn; Dead Beat; 4/27/2006; 5/21/2006
  B0622; Junger, Sebastian; A Death in Belmont; 4/28/2006; 5/28/2006
  B0623; Talese, Gay; A Writer's Life; 5/8/2006; 6/4/2006
  B0624; van Buskirk, James; Celluloid San Francisco; 5/24/2006; 6/11/2006
  B0625; Remnick, David; Reporting - Writings from the New Yorker; 5/17/2006; 6/18/2006
  B0626; Schama, Simon; Rough Crossings; 5/16/2006; 6/25/2006
  B0627; Gavin, James; Intimate Nights: The Golden Age of New York Cabaret; 6/1/2006; 7/2/2006
  B0628; Child, Lee; The Hard Way; 5/30/2006; 7/9/2006
  B0629; Updike, John; Terrorist; 6/8/2006; 7/16/2006
  B0630; Volpe, Joseph; The Toughest Show on Earth - My Rise and Reign at the Metropolitan Opera; 6/1/2006; 7/23/2006
  B0631; Tuaolo, Esera; Alone in the Trenches: My Life as a Gay Man in the NFL; 6/22/2006; 7/30/2006
  B0632; Dean, John; Conservatives without Conscience; 7/28/2006; 8/6/2006
  B0633; Libbey, Ted; The NPR Listener's Encyclopedia of Classical Music; 6/5/2006; 8/13/2006
  B0634; Pitt, Leonard; Walks through Lost Paris: A Journey into the Heart of Historic Paris; 8/2/2006; 8/20/2006
  B0635; Stone, Judy; Not Quite a Memoir: Of Films, Books, the World; 8/17/2006; 8/27/2006
  B0636; Davies, Adam; Goodbye Lemon; 8/9/2006; 9/3/2006
  B0624; van Buskirk, James; Celluloid San Francisco; 5/24/2006; 9/10/2006
  B0637; Winspear, Jacquelline; Messenger of Truth: A Maisie Dobbs Novel; 8/23/2006; 9/17/2006
  B0638; Welsh, Irvine; The Bedroom Secrets of the Master Chefs; 8/22/2006; 9/24/2006
  B0639; Smith, Zadie; On Beauty; 9/14/2006; 10/1/2006
  B0640; Lewis, Michael; The Blind Side: Evolution of a Game; 9/29/2006; 10/8/2006
  B0641; Lopez, Barry; Home Ground: Language for an American Landscape; 10/10/2006; 10/15/2006
  B0642; Albom, Mitch; For One More Day; 10/18/2006; 11/5/2006
  B0643; Hughes, Robert; Things I Didn't Know; 10/18/2006; 11/12/2006
  B0644; Dawkins, Richard; The God Delusion; 10/31/2006; 11/19/2006
  B0645; Lapham, Lewis; Pretensions to Empire: Notes on the Criminal Folly of the Bush Administration; 10/5/2006; 11/26/2006
  B0646; Perlman, Rhea; Otto Undercvover #1: Born to Drive; 11/8/2006; 12/3/2006
  B0647; Suzuki, David; David Suzuki: The Autobiography; 11/9/2006; 12/10/2006
  B0648; Nasaw, David; Andrew Carnegie; 11/3/2006; 12/17/2006
  B0649; Gabler, Neal; Disney - Triumph of the American Imagination; 12/4/2006; 12/24/2006
  B0650; George, Elizabeth; What Came Before He Shot Her; 10/30/2006; 12/31/2006
- 2007 Book Talk Episodes, 2006-2007; 13 digital audio tapes & 1 compact disc (Audio 11)
  Separated Materials note
  The following item from Box 11 has been moved to Box 12 for better long-term storage:
  1 compact disc with a Microsoft Excel document with an index of 2007 digital audio tapes.
  Episode Number; Author Last Name, Author First Name; Book Title; Record Date; Air Date (Length:Minutes)
  B0701; Stone, Erica & Tenzing; Norbu; Himalaya: Personal Stories of Grandeur, Challenge, and Hope; 12/21/2006; 1/7/2007 (:30)
  B0702; Whitehead, Colson; Apex Hides the Hurt; 4/20/2006; 1/14/2007 (:30)
  B0703; Marx, Patricia; Him Her Him Again the End of Him; 1/17/2007; 1/21/2007 (:30)
  B0704; Amis, Martin; House of Meetings; 1/25/2007; 1/28/2007 (:30)
  B0705; Trillin, Calvin; About Alice; 1/26/2007; 2/4/2007 (:30)
  B0706; Klinenberg, Eric; Fighting for Air: The Battle for Control of America's Media; 2/5/2007; 2/11/2007 (:30)
  B0707; Raban, Jonathan; Surveillance; 2/9/2007; 2/18/2007 (:30)
  B0708; Rosenberg, Scott; Dreaming in Code; 2/15/2007; 2/25/2007 (:30)
  B0709; Crook, Elizabeth; The Night Journal; 2/27/2007; 3/4/2007 (:30)
  B0710; Crier, Catherine; Final Analysis - The Untold Story of the Susan Polk Murder Case; 3/5/2007; 3/11/2007 (:30)
  B0711; Sessums, Kevin; Mississippi Sissy; 3/7/2007; 3/18/2007 (:30)
  B0712; Vollmann, William; Poor People; 3/14/2007; 3/25/2007 (:30)
  B0713; Maisel, Eric; A Writer's San Francisco; 2/21/2007; 4/1/2007 (:30)
  B0714; Selznick, Brian; The Invention of Hugo Cabret; 3/14/2007; 4/8/2007 (:30)
  B0715; Dyson, Michael Eric; Debating Race with Michael Eric Dyson; 3/5/2007; 4/15/2007 (:27)
  B0716; Homes, A. M.; The Mistress's Daughter; 4/16/2007; 4/22/2007 (:30)
  B0717; Montandon, Pat; Oh, the Hell of It All; 4/19/2007; 4/29/2007 (:30)
  B0718; van Buskirk, Jim & Boulanger; Robert; Identity Envy; 4/18/2007; 5/6/2007 (:25)
  B0719; Gawande, Atul; Better; 5/1/2007; 5/13/2007 (:30)
  B0720; Bennett, Alan; Untold Stories; 4/27/2007; 5/20/2007 (:30)
  B0721; Chabon, Michael; The Yiddish Policeman's Union; 5/7/2007; 5/27/2007 (:30)
  B0722; Ignatius, David; Body of Lies; 5/4/2007; 6/3/2007 (:30)
  B0723; Brown, Cecil; Dude, Where's My Black Studies Department?; 6/7/2007; 6/10/2007 (:30)
  B0724; Maupin, Armistead; Michael Tolliver Lives; 6/11/2007; 6/17/2007 (:30)
  B0725; Hemingway, John; Strange Tribe - A Family Memoir; 6/12/2007; 6/24/2007 (:30)
  B0726; Ondaatje, Michael; Divisadero; 6/15/2007; 7/1/2007 (:30)
  B0727; Drew, Elizabeth; Richard M. Nixon; 6/19/2007; 7/8/2007 (:30)
  B0728; Rampersad, Arnold; Ralph Ellison; 6/20/2007; 7/15/2007 (:30)
  B0729; Keen, Andrew; The Cult of the Amateur; 7/5/2007; 7/22/2007 (:30)
  B0730; Siler, Julia Flynn; The House of Mondavi; 7/6/2007; 7/29/2007 (:30)
  B0731; Tucker, Michael; Eikenberry; Jill; Living in a Foreign Language; 7/26/2007; 8/5/2007 (:30)
  B0732; Fforde, Jasper; First among Sequels; 7/30/2007; 8/12/2007 (:30)
  B0733; Drucker, Eugene; Savior; 8/1/2007; 8/19/2007 (:30)
  B0734; Thomson, Rupert; Death of a Murderer; 8/13/2007; 8/26/2007 (:30)
  B0735; Pitts, David; Jack and Lem; 8/29/2007; 9/2/2007 (:30)
  B0736; Newhouse, Dave; The Bears; 8/24/2007; 9/9/2007 (:60)
  B0737; Tramble, Thomas; Tramble; Wilma; Pullman Porters and West Oakland; 9/12/2007; 9/16/2007 (:17)
  B0737; Spanogle, Joshua; Flawless; 9/11/2007; 9/16/2007 (:24)
  B0738; Lam, Vincent; Bloodletting and Miraculous Cures; 9/17/2007; 9/23/2007 (:30)
  B0739; Adams, Lisa; John; Why We Read What We Read; 9/27/2007; 9/30/2007 (:30)
  B0740; Draper, Robert; Dead Certain; 10/3/2007; 10/7/2007 (:30)
  B0741; Toobin, Jeffrey; The Nine; 10/3/2007; 10/14/2007 (:30)
  B0742; Mosley, Walter; Blonde Faith; 10/11/2007; 11/4/2007 (:30)
  B0743; Kavanagh, Julie; Nureyev: The Life; 10/12/2007; 11/11/2007 (:30)
  B0744; Danticat, Edwidge; Brother, I'm Dying; 10/16/2007; 11/18/2007 (:30)
  B0745; Sacks, Oliver; Musicophilia: Stories of Music and the Brain; 10/2/2007; 11/25/2007 (:30)
  B0746; Krugman, Paul; The Conscience of a Liberal; 10/31/2007; 12/9/2007 (:30)
  B0747; Kalman, Maira; Principles of Uncertainty; 10/31/2007; 12/9/2007 (:30)
  B0748; Ross, Alex; The Rest Is Noise: Listening to the 20th Century; 10/19/2007; 12/16/2007 (:30)
  B0749; Michaelis, David; Schultz and Peanuts: A Biography; 11/9/2007; 12/23/2007 (:30)
  B0750; Kennedy, Matthew; Kpan Blondell - A Life between Takes; 12/6/2007; 12/30/2007 (:30)